Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Musical Recordings, 6 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 4 flat boxes, 1 LP box, and 1 flat file.; 192 audiocassettes; 94 sound tape reels; 2 sound discs (vinyl); 42.34 Gigabytes in 1,741 digital files.
  - ESP Sampler with Alan Sondheim, Undated; cuid35002 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_164)
    Note says "Happy Chanukah Alan"
  - "ETC", Undated; cuid39763 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_198)
  - "Fifty-Six" by Alan Sondheim, Qbico Records, 2007; cuid39712 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_79)
  - "Flute" Digital Audio Series, 2003; cuid39721 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_89)
  - France / Dance Master, Undated; cuid34883 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_272)
    Duration: 60 minutes.
  - From the Theatre Piece, Undated; cuid34800 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_080)
  - The Garden Planet Revisited by Jacki Apple, Undated; cuid35047 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_202)
  - "Gatha" Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39722 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_90)
  - Geoff Dugan - The Aluminum Hallway, Undated; cuid35008 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_171)
    The cassette includes a tracklist.
    Duration: 56 minutes.
  - Geoff Dugan - Base Animal, 1989; cuid34873 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_373)
  - Glossolalia, Undated; cuid35043 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_198)
  - Good Electronics, Undated; cuid30290 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_111)
    Duration: 80 minutes. Preservation note: Content sounds like it's being played back at the wrong speed; this was probably a delibrate effect.
  - Great Electronics, Undated; cuid34797 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_086)
  - Group Concert Pieces, Undated; cuid30294 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_115)
    Duration: 30 minutes; Preservation note: Severely deformed tape.
  - "Grut Compex" Digital Audio Series, 2006; cuid39723 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_91)
  - Guitar, April, 1975; cuid34937 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_207)
  - Guitar and Building Resonance, Undated; cuid34945 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_215)
  - "Guitar" and "D.G. Guitar" Digital Audio Series, 2003-2009; cuid39724 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_92)
  - Guitar / Sonfist, Undated; cuid35021 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_182)
  - Hanni Neyor / Sleepy Volume Estes, Rosalie Sorrels, Undated; cuid35035 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_193)
  - Harmonica / Airline, Undated; cuid34887 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_276)
  - Harmonica Digital Audio Series, 2006-2009; cuid39756 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_124)
  - Harmonics - [Illegible] ETC, November, 2002; cuid34927 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_315)
  - "Harp" Digital Audio Series, 2006; cuid39725 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_93)
  - "Hasapi" Digital Audio Series, 2009; cuid39726 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_94)
  - Hazel Nuts - Alvin Curran, May 9, 1971; cuid34819 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_062)
    Duration: 11 minutes.
  - Heavily Distorted Voices and Sounds, Sex Tape, Undated; cuid35075 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_237)
    Duration: 96 minutes.
    Content warning: this recording includes strong sexual content.
  - Heavy Echo with Guitar - Hiss, Undated; cuid34805 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_042)
    Duration: 10 minutes.
  - Hollywood Boulevard Sounds / Carrie on Jim / Short Section / Piano Modulation, Undated; cuid34903 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_294)
    Duration: 40 minutes; Preservation note: Content has distorted flutter sound, unclear if intentional or due to deterioration.
  - Hornpipes Firenze Concert (Bill, Viola, Art, Topes), April, 1975; cuid34838 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_326)
    Duration: 56 minutes; Preservation note: Muted sound.
  - Hornpipes Practice Session with Bill Viola, Undated; cuid34998 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_160)
  - Horns, Undated; cuid35023 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_184)
    Duration: 103 minutes.
  - Hot Mud, Undated; cuid34896 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_287)
  - Humans ETC, 2000; cuid34987 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_148)
  - I. Sections Wound Backwards / Magnetic Tape Readout Piece, Undated; cuid34820 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_061)
  - I'm Sorry I… Heather / Alan, Undated; cuid34962 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_234, Box 14, Audiocassette 267_371)
  - Improvisations by Derek Bailey and David Holland, January, 1971; cuid30314 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_137)
    The tape's label reads, "Improvisations; Derek Bailey - Guitar; David Holland - Cello; Live in London, January, 1971"
  - International Folk Music Compilation, October 31, 1969; cuid34816 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_097)
    This recording includes songs from Ethiopia, Romania, Hungary, Lithuania, Persia, and Colombia. The tape has a label from the Department of Music at Brown University,
  - "Ion" Digital Audio Series, 2005; cuid39727 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_95)
  - "Irish" Digital Audio Series, 2007; cuid39728 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_96)
  - Jacques Cartier, Undated; cuid34905 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_296)
  - Jarboe, 1984; cuid34835 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_462)
  - Joanna - Mighty Risen Plea Records, Undated; cuid34854 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_346)
  - Kim Il Sung 70th Birthday - Radio North Korea Pyongyang, April 15, 1982; cuid34842 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_330)
    The label also says "9977 on dial - 3:00am - 4:10am L.A."
  - Kim Il Sung ETC Soundtrack Music, Undated; cuid34992 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_154)
    Duration: 59 minutes; Preservation note: Poor audio reception with distortion and speed issues.
  - Kimilsungism [Illegible] Analysis I, Undated; cuid34890 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_280)
  - Koto Tummy, Undated; cuid35022 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_183)
  - Krishnamurti and Me, Ken Kesey and Merry Pranksters, Undated; cuid34918 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_310)
  - "Kronecker Delta" Digital Audio Series, 2009; cuid39729 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_97)
  - Last Fighter in the Bolshevick Revolution, Undated; cuid34957 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_227)
  - Last Night Mix Tape, Undated; cuid34824 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_069, 267_070, 267_073, 267_083)
  - Late Piece with Synthesizer, June, Undated; cuid30297 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_118)
    Duration: 65 minutes. Preservation note: Content on the two tracks is mostly the same, but they don't quite sync up; they have been left as two files.
  - Laura and Alan, Undated; cuid34982 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_263)
    Duration: 70 minutes.
  - Lockin' in Harmonies / Normal Voice Encoding at Subharmonies, Undated; cuid34942 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_212)
  - Long Devonner Improvisation Material All Side, Undated; cuid34860 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_354)
  - "Lowery" Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39730 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_98)
  - "Lumber" Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39731 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_99)
  - "Luna" Digital Audio Series, 2010; cuid39732 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_100)
  - "LW" Digital Audio Series, 2006; cuid39733 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_101)
  - Lynn Hughes full script, news special, Undated; cuid34971 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_249)
  - Mandolin, Piano, ETC, and Reading into Piano, Undated; cuid35034 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_192)
  - Marcia Resnick, Undated; cuid34950 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_221)
  - Mariel Boatlift - Nighlirr [Illegible], November 23, 1987; cuid34891 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_281)
  - Mariner, Undated; cuid34951 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_222)
  - Master / Slave Relationship: Sound of Pig Music #82, Undated; cuid34984 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_145)
    Duration: 55 minutes.
  - Matrix, Undated; cuid35019 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_180)
  - "Meditate" Digital Audio Series, 2006-2009; cuid39734 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_102)
  - "Melody" Digital Audio Series, 2006; cuid39735 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_103)
  - Meta Notes / Heartbeat Tape, Undated; cuid34878 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_266)
  - Meta Thinktank, 1972; cuid34991 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_152)
  - Michael Oppitz Interview, May 4, 1986; cuid34864 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_359)
    Duration: 88 minutes.
  - Middle 6, Middle 14, Undated; cuid34966 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_243)
  - MIDI Audio Files, 1996-1998; cuid39757 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_125)
  - Mighty Risen Plea, Undated; cuid35007 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_170)
  - Minntemen, Undated; cuid34936 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_206)
    Duration: 82 minutes.
  - "Modern" Digital Audio Series, 2006; cuid39736 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_104)
  - "Mono" Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39737 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_105)
  - "Morse" Digital Audio Series, 2006; cuid39738 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_106)
  - Mr Mrs Accident - Cornfield Ears, 1987; cuid34912 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_303)
  - Mouse Music, Undated; cuid34974 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_253)
    Duration: 48 minutes.
  - Murmurs, Undated; cuid34977 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_255)
    Duration: 44 minutes.
  - Music [illegible], Undated; cuid35016 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_178)
  - Music by Terry Firenze / Music with Teddy Fox, Bill, Viola Florence, Undated; cuid34837 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_325)
  - Music for its Erhea [Illegible], Undated; cuid34810 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_047)
  - Musical Performances - Circuitry Diagrams, Undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Musical Performances - Set Lists and Notes, Undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Musical Performances - Stage Setup Diagrams, Undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Muzak - QtP, Undated; cuid34871 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_370)
  - Myk and Alan Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39758 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_126)
  - New Tape, Undated; cuid34802 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_045)
    Duration: 87 minutes.
  - New York Women Tape, August 8, 1975; cuid35038 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_181, 267_195)
  - Niagra Falls, Heather College, Undated; cuid34969 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_246)
  - "Node" Digital Audio Series, 2004-2009; cuid39739 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_107)
  - Nostalgic Tape, Undated; cuid34798 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_075)
    Duration: 19 minutes. Preservation notes: the recording has different content in the left and right channels; due to the experimental nature of the collection it was not possible to determine whether the two tracks were meant to be together or separated, so they have been left together.
  - Notes on Aesthetics, European and Amer. [illegible], Undated; cuid35015 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_178)
  - Notes Then Mandolin, Dawana Reading, Undated; cuid34929 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_319)
  - NSCAD Guitar / Pulse Concert / Dual Conversation / part NSCAD Guitar Concert / Patternless loud Drumming / fast / Pattern Change ETC, Undated; cuid35018 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_180)
  - O to 253: Sound FM; Memory Film, Undated; cuid34856 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_348)
  - Object Into Sound - Translation Utilizing Half-Inch Grid, Undated; cuid34830 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_077)
  - Object Into Sound - Translation Using Five Inch Grid, September 22, 1969; cuid34910 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_302)
  - "Oboe" Digital Audio Series, 2003-2008; cuid39740 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_108)
  - Old Group Streusto [Illegible] Pro-Recording, Undated; cuid34803 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_044)
  - Old Tape with Gretch Guitar, Undated; cuid30293 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_114)
    A note on the tape says, "Beautiful - don't lose."
  - "Oo" Digital Audio Series, 2010; cuid39741 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_109)
  - "Oratorio" Sheet Music, Undated (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Organ / Hughes / News, Undated; cuid35045 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_200)
  - Organ Tape: Eva Sue Szela, URI, circa 1966; cuid34814 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_098)
  - Organ Tape: URI Thomas, Church Organ, 1966; cuid30306 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_128)
    Duration: 13 minutes.
  - Organ Tape for Reed Point, Undated; cuid34963 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_238)
  - Patricia Rogers, Undated; cuid30302 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_122)
  - Paul B / N. Kitchel Notes + Notes on Pieces, Eyeing, Novel, Etc., Undated; cuid34845 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_333)
  - Paula Claire and the Paxton Group Performances, Undated; cuid34938 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_208)
    This tape contains poetry and musical performances by Paula Claire and the Paxton Group, which includes Steven Paxton, John Griffith, Ray Dillard, and Cynthia Cole. Performances include "Spiderunes," "The Dundee Telgrams, "The Patmost Poems," "Still Life," "Zen Inscriptions," "Through Glass," and "OIF."
  - Percussive Electronic Sound, Undated; cuid35071 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_217)
    Duration: 5 minutes.
  - "Pesach" Digital Audio Series, 2010; cuid39742 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_110)
  - Pia Zastera, Undated; cuid34939 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_209)
  - Piano, Undated; cuid35017 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_179)
    Duration: 37 minutes.
  - "Pieds" Digital Audio Series, 2006-2009; cuid39743 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_111)
  - Political Third Tape, Undated; cuid35048 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_203)
    Duration: 49 minutes.
  - "Pophit" Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39744 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_112)
  - Post-Conceptual Act, RISD, March 19, 1974; cuid34881 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_270)
  - Potential Propaganda…, Undated; cuid34906 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_297)
    Duration: 60 minutes; Preservation note: content has distorted flutter sound, unclear if intentional or due to deterioration.
  - "Prespace", 2005; cuid39764 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_199)
    From the disc label: "9 guitar works recorded flat with 1920 Larson parlor guitar. Audio works from VLF (very low frequency) recording. Audio works from VLF audio recording with frequency shifting. Audio works with tottering granular synthesis. A subset of VLF radio signals are ducted in the atmosphere. Digital modifications of such signal transform ducting into inhabited space. Nearby movement in moist conditions couples and uncouples antenna operation." Santa Ana, California, Grand Central Press
  - "Qin" Digital Audio Series, 2010; cuid39745 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_113)
  - The Quran, Undated; cuid34985 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_146)
    Duration: 35 minutes.
  - "Radio", Undated; cuid39765 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_200)
  - Radio Program in French, Undated; cuid35081 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_204)
  - Rapping, Undated; cuid35032 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_190)
  - The Raven / The History of Album Rock [Empty Audiotape Box], Undated; cuid34817 (Box 25, Box 267_108)
  - Reagan Shooting / Music for Brazil, September, 1979; cuid34900 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_291)
  - Recorded Songs, Undated; cuid35083 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_096)
    Duration: 76 minutes.
  - Reed Point / British Census of Hallucinations / Brasil I, Undated; cuid35039 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_196)
  - "Requiem Digitatem" by Mia Lipner, a special audio installment for Vol 9, No. 1, Issue 17: "Sexuality & Cyberspace", 1996; cuid34859 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_353)
    Duration: 27 minutes.
  - Reversed Dulemei [illegible] Master, Undated; cuid30299 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_120)
  - Rhythm Pieces, Chant, August, 1986; cuid34972 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_250)
  - "Riff A" and "Riff B" Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39746 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_114)
  - RISD Concert Tape, Undated; cuid30307 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_134)
  - RISD Semi-Electronic with Guitar Feedback, February 2, 1971; cuid34815 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_100)
    Duration: 80 minutes.
  - Ritual All-7-70: "ESP Disk", Undated; cuid39766 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_201)
    This album was marketed and distributed by ZYX-Music GmbH.
  - Ritual-All-7-70: "T'Other Little Tune" ESP-DISK Poster, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Ritual-All-7-70 I, Undated; cuid34801 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_076)
  - Ritual-All-7-70 II, Undated; cuid34807 (Box 81, Quarter inch audio reel 267_091)
  - Ritual-All-7-70 III, Undated; cuid34808 (Box 22, Quarter inch audio reel 267_092)
  - Ritual-All-7-70 V, Undated; cuid30295 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_116)
  - Ritual-All-7-70 IV, Undated; cuid34796 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_085)
    Duration: 39 minutes.
  - Ritual-All-7-70 - The Songs, circa 1967-1970; cuid35092 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_312, Box 13, Audiocassette 267_165, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_204)
    Audiocassette 267_312's label notes Songs 1 "Reading University Great Hall, Hammond Organ Harmoniums, Piano Percussion" and Songs 2 "Wesleyan University Connecticut, USA, Electric Piano, Electric Organ and Filters."
  - Ritual-All-7-70 - The Songs - Irregular Pulses, Unique Marks, November, 1970; cuid34941 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_211)
    Duration: 101 minutes.
  - Ritual-All-7-70 - Original Take of The Songs (Clean), 1967; cuid34812 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_094)
    Duration: 166 minutes.
  - Ritual-All-7-70 - Performance Flyers, Programs, and Press, 1967-1971 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Ritual-All-7-70 - Rehearsal for The Songs, circa 1967; cuid34822 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_057)
  - Ritual-All-7-70 - Set list and performance notes, Undated (Flat-file-folder 20, Folder 20)
  - Roger Treiutley, Undated; cuid34799 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_063)
  - "Rough Mixes" Digital Audio Series, 2010; cuid39747 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_115)
  - Sagging and Reading Room, "It Doesn't Sound Like Me" and "Catch Up" Video Installations, Undated; cuid34922 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_312)
    The cassette's label notes that the video installation was at Serpentine Galleries in London.
  - St. Mark's Performance - Stations of the Cross, June, 1974; cuid34857 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_351)
  - Sampler Music, Undated; cuid34840 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_328)
  - Sampling, Saw, Tone, Undated; cuid30298 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_119)
  - Save ESP - Original, First Record, Undated; cuid34829 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_071)
  - Self Introduction - Alan Sondheim, Undated; cuid34931 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_321)
    Duration: 6 minutes.
  - Semi Piece and Pulse Echo Piece / Withdrawn in Context of a Conversation, Undated; cuid35013 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_177)
  - Sentence Message, Piece: Notes on Linguistic Pieces, Glossolalia, Undated; cuid35030 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_189)
  - Separation Beth ETC Reading, March 16, 1974; cuid35033 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_191)
    Label reads "Separation Beth / Violation Fabric / Burned Out' Sequence / Skin Surface (her) / Conclusion"
  - Sheet Music, 1957-1971 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Sine Coding Into Subharmonies, October 20, 1970; cuid34915 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_307)
  - Six Chansons - Hindemith (Vocal Ensemble), May 12, 1965; cuid34809 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_050)
  - Skin, Undated; cuid34909 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_301)
  - Skin Surface - David A. [illegible] Etc. Conversation, Undated; cuid34852 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_344)
  - "Slidin'… some slide" - various, plus George Thorogood, Undated; cuid35005 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_169)
  - Slow Type / Computer / art fest, Undated; cuid35027 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_187)
  - Solo Musical Performances - Flyers, Playbills, Ephemera, circa 1975-2005 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Solo Sampler - Alan Sondheim, Undated; cuid34826 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_065)
    Other labels on the box say "History of Album Rock" and "Lord Peter Whimsey Five Red Herrings"
  - Some Clark Coolidge, Undated; cuid34804 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_043)
  - Someone Dies, Undated; cuid35003 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_167)
  - Sound Samples and Ambient Recordings, 1994-2009; cuid39759 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_127)
  - Source Material, Undated; cuid34827 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_064)
    The tape includes "Freedom Yes, Apartheid No," "No More Porn," and Woodpecker Signal. Another label on the tape says "Beatles White Album."
  - Speech Act / Dial Tone / Notes on Time, Undated; cuid35041 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_197)
  - Speech Variation / Amplitude / Pitch / Accent / Timbre, Time / (laughter) / patternless tap dancing, Undated; cuid35042 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_198)
  - "STE" Digital Audio Series, 2008-2009; cuid39748 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_116)
  - Stelarc, October 16, 2000; cuid34841 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_329, 267_338)
  - Sub Sax Toronto, August, 1980; cuid34846 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_334)
  - Sue Cole / Reading (bod) Sue Cole, Undated; cuid34993 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_155)
  - Sunshine / Discourse / Gunther with Blockage, Undated; cuid34899 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_290)
  - Susan Hoover, September 23, 1970; cuid30305 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_126)
  - T'Other Little Tune, 1968; cuid35090 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_369, Box 13, Audiocassette 267_166, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_206)
  - T'Other Little Tune Vinyl Photos, circa 1969 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Taped from Carry Nations, Undated; cuid35011 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_174)
  - Tasmania Soundtrack / Sex Master, Undated; cuid34913 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_304)
    Content warning: Side two contains explicit sexual content.
  - "Taxi" Digital Audio Series, 2006; cuid39749 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_117)
  - "Tenor Banjo" Digital Audio Series, 2008-2009; cuid39750 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_118)
  - Test Tape - Alan Counting and Whistling, Undated; cuid35070 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_283)
    Duration: 1 minute.
  - Tinnitus - "Demur" and "Phragmacone" Live, 1988-1989; cuid34925 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_313)
  - Tired, January 10, 1968; cuid30289 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_110)
    Tape label reads: "Jane Fellows - vocal; John Eugh [illegible] - Tenor Sax; Greg Johnson - Flute; Alan Sondheim - Bells, Gongs, Orchestral Bells, Xylophone, Marimba, Sarod, Slide Whistle, Hawaiian Guitar; Also: Filters, Bass-Treble Amps, 2 tape recorders, organ drone, guitar amp, mixer"
  - "Tobin" Digital Audio Series, 2008; cuid39751 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_119)
  - Tracy, Undated; cuid34932 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_322)
  - Two-Timer: Canada Time, Undated; cuid34946 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_216)
  - "Ukulele" Digital Audio Series, 2009; cuid39752 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_120)
  - "Unbalanced" by Alan Sondheim and Matt Frantz, 2005; cuid39767 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_202)
    1920 acoustic parlor guitar: (Reb) Alan Sondheim; Electronics, electric guitar, electric bass, production: Matt Frantz
  - Music Concert - "Union Gap"; "Young Girl"; "Vanilla Fudge", 1968; cuid30296 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_117)
    Duration: 17 minutes; Preservation note: Much of the content is deliberately in reverse.
    The label reads, "Trombone backwards; June with Filter, Guitar, Flute and Clarinet"
  - Spoken Narratives and Poetry Interspersed with Music, 1980; cuid34904 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_295)
    The spoken narratives on side A are mostly about travels in Montreal, Toronto and Quebec.
  - Untitled String Series, 2005-2006; cuid39760 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_128)
  - Various Music Samples, Undated; cuid35065 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_081)